Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I am doing.
してます
why?
なんで?
Because I don't.
しないから
Like Hamedori?
はめどりみたいな?
Have you never done it?
してことない?
I've never done it before.
もうしたことない
Ah, I've done that before.
あ、したことあるんだよ
Only once.
1回だけ
There is.
あるんだ
How?
どういうふうに?
With my boyfriend...
彼氏と...
When I put it in...
入れてるときに...
on second thoughts...
やっぱり...
Ah, I see.
ああ、なるほどね
My boyfriend...
彼氏が...
That's it.
それだけ
Is that all?
それだけ?
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ
It's below.
下でしょ
Don't hide it.
隠さないで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Please put it in.
入れてください
It's beautiful, isn't it?
綺麗だよね
amazing.
すごい
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
dangerous.
あぶない
Good luck, with both hands.
頑財してよ、両手で
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's not good anymore.
もうちょっとダメ
Really.
本当に
why?
なんで?
Really without it.
本当に無しで
I really want to go back to sleep without it.
本当に無しで寝返したい
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
No more.
もうダメ
why?
なんで?
Really.
本当に
please.
お願いします
Is it a visual process?
見処理なの?
No, I said it was a visual process.
いや、見処理言ったわけね
Please go there in the summer as well.
夏も行ってもらって
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
But no.
でも、やだ
No way.
やだ
I kind of forgot about it.
ちょっと忘れてたから
I haven't even checked.
確認すらしてないから
picture?
え?
I got wet.
濡れちゃった
Are you going to make it that bright?
そんな明るくするんですか?
When photographing there.
そこを撮るときは
I got wet.
濡れちゃった
fault.
あら
Really.
本当に
Are you excited?
興奮しちゃったの?
I'm trying to touch it.
触ろうとしてる
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
It's not pretty.
綺麗無しだね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
It's really difficult.
本当に難しい
You shot it beautifully.
綺麗に撮ってるね
I'm a legend myself.
自分でさ、伝説でさ
It's wet.
濡れてる
You'll get wet.
濡れちゃうんですよ
Put some power together.
ちょっとパワー組んで
like this?
こう?
Well then,
じゃあ、
It closes really well.
す っごい閉まる
why?
なんで?
It closed on its own.
勝手に閉まったよね
It was interesting.
面白かった